<jokes>
	<joke>
		<id>1</id>
		<author>Jack Canfield</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leaders cannot work in a vacuum. They may take on larger, seemingly more important roles in an organization, but this does not exclude them from asking for and using feedback. In fact, a leader arguably needs feedback more so than anyone else. It's what helps a leader respond appropriately to events in pursuit of successful outcomes.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>2</id>
		<author>Rafael Cruz</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I grew up in Cuba under a strong, military, oppressive dictatorship. So as a teenager, I found myself involved in a revolution. I remember during that time, a young, charismatic leader rose up, talking about hope and change. His name was Fidel Castro.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>3</id>
		<author>Rosalynn Carter</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader takes people where they want to go. A great leader takes people where they don't necessarily want to go, but ought to be.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>4</id>
		<author>Henry A. Kissinger</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It is, after all, the responsibility of the expert to operate the familiar and that of the leader to transcend it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>5</id>
		<author>Jay-Z</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Hip-hop has done so much for racial relations, and I don't think it's given the proper credit. It has changed America immensely. I'm going to make a very bold statement: Hip-hop has done more than any leader, politician, or anyone to improve race relations.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>6</id>
		<author>Tom Stoppard</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The notion that the 'leader' has the right to ask huge sacrifices of your generation for a notional future paradise - if you'd be good enough to lie down under the wheels of the juggernaut - that sentimental and self-aggrandising rationalisation for brute force and cowardice I felt from adolescence was wrong.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>7</id>
		<author>Ayn Rand</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The man who lets a leader prescribe his course is a wreck being towed to the scrap heap.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>8</id>
		<author>Charles de Gaulle</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A true leader always keeps an element of surprise up his sleeve, which others cannot grasp but which keeps his public excited and breathless.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>9</id>
		<author>Walter Lippmann</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The final test of a leader is that he leaves behind him in other men the conviction and the will to carry on.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>10</id>
		<author>Chris Christie</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The job of a leader, the job of a governor, the job of a president, is to get the people in the room and bang enough heads together and rub enough arms and cajole enough to have them put the country and the state's greater interest ahead of their own personal partisan interest. That's what we did in New Jersey and that's the model for America.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>11</id>
		<author>Leymah Gbowee</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership is standing with your people. People say you have to live to fight another day, but sometimes you have to show you are a true leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>12</id>
		<author>Patricia Hill Collins</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Social conditions that spur large numbers of people into action are ignored in favor of a Hollywood version of history focusing on one conquering hero. Since a movement for social change is embodied in its leader, death of the leader means death of the movement.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>13</id>
		<author>Vince Lombardi</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader can never close the gap between himself and the group. If he does, he is no longer what he must be. He must walk a tightrope between the consent he must win and the control he must exert.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>14</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>To remain a credible leader, I must always work first, hardest, and longest on changing myself. This is neither easy nor natural, but it is essential.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>15</id>
		<author>Harry S Truman</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader in the Democratic Party is a boss, in the Republican Party he is a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>16</id>
		<author>Newt Gingrich</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I'm not a natural leader. I'm too intellectual; I'm too abstract; I think too much.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>17</id>
		<author>Ezra Taft Benson</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Disobedience is essentially a prideful power struggle against someone in authority over us. It can be a parent, a priesthood leader, a teacher, or ultimately God. A proud person hates the fact that someone is above him. He thinks this lowers his position.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>18</id>
		<author>James E. Faust</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader must be a good listener. He must be willing to take counsel. He must show a genuine concern and love for those under his stewardship.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>19</id>
		<author>Howard Gardner</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Stories are the single most powerful tool in a leader's toolkit.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>20</id>
		<author>Ashton Kutcher</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I'm not a follower of this or that religious leader. More wars are started because of religious leaders, and people are following and they don't know why... That is religiosity. That is what turns people into robots.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>21</id>
		<author>Anne Sweeney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A good leader should focus on making sure everyone is being given the tools to do their job, not just expecting - poof! - that they're going to produce great work.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>22</id>
		<author>John Keegan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader of men in warfare can show himself to his followers only through a mask, a mask that he must make for himself, but a mask made in such form as will mark him to men of his time and place as the leader they want and need.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>23</id>
		<author>Valentina Tereshkova</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Russia is still the leader in world space exploration. But its position of leader involves great responsibility - we have no right to lag behind. We can and we must move constantly forward.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>24</id>
		<author>Dalai Lama</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I always believe the rule by king or official leader is outdated. Now we must catch up with the modern world.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>25</id>
		<author>Albert Camus</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>One leader, one people, signifies one master and millions of slaves.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>26</id>
		<author>Zig Ziglar</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It will be disastrous when a leader or manager shows up with one attitude one day and treats people with a different attitude the next day.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>27</id>
		<author>Barack Obama</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If you're looking for the safe choice, you shouldn't be supporting a black guy named Barack Obama to be the next leader of the free world.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>28</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If you are a leader, you should never forget that everyone needs encouragement. And everyone who receives it - young or old, successful or less-than-successful, unknown or famous - is changed by it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>29</id>
		<author>Eric Hoffer</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader has to be practical and a realist, yet must talk the language of the visionary and the idealist.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>30</id>
		<author>Hermann Hesse</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Those who cannot think or take responsibility for themselves need, and clamor for, a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>31</id>
		<author>Henry A. Kissinger</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader who confines his role to his people's experience dooms himself to stagnation; a leader who outstrips his people's experience runs the risk of not being understood.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>32</id>
		<author>Charles de Gaulle</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader must aim high, see big, judge widely, thus setting himself apart form the ordinary people who debate in narrow confines.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>33</id>
		<author>Joe DiMaggio</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A person always doing his or her best becomes a natural leader, just by example.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>34</id>
		<author>John Updike</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is one who, out of madness or goodness, volunteers to take upon himself the woe of the people. There are few men so foolish, hence the erratic quality of leadership in the world.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>35</id>
		<author>Ann Coulter</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As the leader of twelve apostles, even Jesus had more executive experience than Obama.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>36</id>
		<author>Margaret Atwood</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>We still think of a powerful man as a born leader and a powerful woman as an anomaly.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>37</id>
		<author>Nina Hagen</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Jesus Christ will be the leader of an intergalactic earth evacuation. We're getting some earth leaders up there to check the mother ship. The Bible says that the sky will be glorious and Christ will come back to us all.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>38</id>
		<author>Sam Rayburn</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>You cannot be a leader, and ask other people to follow you, unless you know how to follow, too.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>39</id>
		<author>Jimmy Carter</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Billy Graham is one of my great lifetime heroes. I think he epitomizes the essence of what a Christian leader should be. I have participated in some of his crusades a couple of times in Atlanta. I've seen the profound impact he's had on me personally, and on other people who were not Christians and accepted Christ as Savior.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>40</id>
		<author>Madeleine Albright</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As a leader, you have to have the ability to assimilate new information and understand that there might be a different view.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>41</id>
		<author>Malala Yousafzai</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Benazir Bhutto was an inspirational leader and an inspirational woman.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>42</id>
		<author>Ariel Sharon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Netanyahu is pressured easily, gets into a panic, and loses his senses... to run a country like Israel a leader needs to have reason and judgment and nerves of steel, two traits he does not have.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>43</id>
		<author>Dolores Huerta</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>My mother was a dominant force in our family. And I always saw her as the leader. And that was great for me as a young woman, because I never saw that women had to be dominated by men.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>44</id>
		<author>Douglas Conant</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership does take work. And it should. If you aspire to be a leader, you ought to treat leadership as a craft, you ought to become a student of it, and you ought to work at it. And if you're not willing to work at it, well, you get what you give.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>45</id>
		<author>Warren Bennis</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The manager has his eye on the bottom line; the leader has his eye on the horizon.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>46</id>
		<author>Cesar Millan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Americans are very big about loving the dog first, so when you tell them you have to set rules and limitations, a lot of people believe it's going to hurt their feelings. They're actually looking for you to be the pack leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>47</id>
		<author>Michael Porter</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If your goal is anything but profitability - if it's to be big, or to grow fast, or to become a technology leader - you'll hit problems.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>48</id>
		<author>Alexander Chase</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>People, like sheep, tend to follow a leader - occasionally in the right direction.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>49</id>
		<author>John Forbes Nash, Jr.</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I know that if I could really understand mental illness, then it would be appropriate to make a big career shift. I would become a therapist and a leader in terms of mental illness. But I'm not in the position.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>50</id>
		<author>Seth Godin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Being a leader gives you charisma. If you look and study the leaders who have succeeded, that's where charisma comes from, from the leading.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>51</id>
		<author>Hakeem Olajuwonw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>All these boundaries - Africa, Asia, Malaysia, America - are set by men. But you don't have to look at boundaries when you are looking at a man - at the character of a man. The question is: What do you stand for? Are you a follower, or are you a leader?</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>52</id>
		<author>Thomas Frankw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As it happens, Chicago is the nation's leader in municipal privatization efforts. That's right: The city that conservatives portray as the citadel of the power-grabbing, government-growing left has been selling itself off in pieces for years. It signed a 99-year lease for the Chicago Skyway, a toll road in the city's South Side, back in 2005.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>53</id>
		<author>Mikhail Gorbachevw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I couldn't wait to get to the most powerful position, because I thought then I would be able to fix problems that only the leader can fix. But when I got there, I realized we needed revolutionary change.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>54</id>
		<author>Shari Arisonw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Change is not in the hands of government, not in the hands of a leader or guru, and not in the hands of the powerful or wealthy. It is in our hands: the hands of each and every one of us.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>55</id>
		<author>Nick Cleggw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Although I am a young leader, I actually came to it strangely quite late. I have a different perspective, partly because of my family, partly because of what I did for ten years: negotiating trade deals, working out in Central Asia doing assistance projects.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>56</id>
		<author>Skylar Greyw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I would say that nobody is going to work harder for your career than yourself - the one with the vision. No matter how many people you hire, nobody is going to get is as much as yourself does. So it's really important to be your own leader at all times and not hand it all off, otherwise the whole empire will fall apart.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>57</id>
		<author>Mark Warnerw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Virginia is the absolute leader in homeland security and defense and information technology.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>58</id>
		<author>Leonard Slatkinw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The conductor is the artistic leader and sometimes cultural arbiter of his or her community. It is their leadership that is looked to and should anything go wrong, they are the persons taking most of the heat.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>59</id>
		<author>Tom Lantosw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader of Iran made one of the most repugnant remarks the international community has heard since Adolf Hitler.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>60</id>
		<author>Dalai Lamaw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I want to be just a pure spiritual leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>61</id>
		<author>Dalai Lamaw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The Dalai Lama is just a temporal leader of Tibet.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>62</id>
		<author>Bill Gatesw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It's OK for China to invent cancer drugs that cure patients in the United States. We want them to catch up. But as the leader, we want to keep setting a very, very high standard. We don't want them to catch up because we're slowing down or, even worse, going into reverse.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>63</id>
		<author>Bill Gatesw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>With tech companies, whoever's the leader is always questioned, you know. They say, 'Is this the end of them?' And - there's more - more times people think that's the case than it really is the case.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>64</id>
		<author>Barack Obamaw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>We all remember Abraham Lincoln as the leader who saved our Union. Founder of the Republican Party.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>65</id>
		<author>Alice Walkerw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I can easily imagine Obama sitting down and talking to any leader - or any person - in the world, with no baggage of past servitude or race supremacy to mar their talks.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>66</id>
		<author>Desmond Tutuw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Peace comes when you talk to the guy you most hate. And that's where the courage of a leader comes, because when you sit down with your enemy, you as a leader must already have very considerable confidence from your own constituency.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>67</id>
		<author>Henri Nouwenw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The Christian leader of the future is called to be completely irrelevant and to stand in this world with nothing to offer but his or her own vulnerable self. God loves us, not because of what we do or accomplish, but because God has created and redeemed us in love.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>68</id>
		<author>Desmond Tutuw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am a leader by default, only because nature does not allow a vacuum.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>69</id>
		<author>Noam Chomskyw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As a Zionist youth leader in the 1940s, I was among those who called for a binational state in Mandatory Palestine. When a Jewish state was declared, I felt that it should have the rights of other states - no more, no less.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>70</id>
		<author>Charles R. Swindollw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I'm not against screens, or new songs, or innovation. I just don't like the gimmicks. I want to know when worship is over that that leader's sole purpose was to glorify the Lord Jesus Christ.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>71</id>
		<author>Bo Bennettw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A good leader is one who can tell another how to reach his or her potential; a great leader is one who can help another discover this potential for him or herself.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>72</id>
		<author>Benjamin Disraeliw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I must follow the people. Am I not their leader?</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>73</id>
		<author>Mitt Romneyw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The country already has a leader who divides us with the bitter politics of envy. We have to offer an alternative vision.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>74</id>
		<author>Henry Rollinsw</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>In the city of Pyongyang, you don't have to look very far to see an image of the Great Leader, Kim Il Sung. They love the guy. He is responsible for the wonder that is North Korea.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>75</id>
		<author>Andre Maurois</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The most important quality in a leader is that of being acknowledged as such. All leaders whose fitness is questioned are clearly lacking in force.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>76</id>
		<author>Mitt Romney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Internationally, President Obama has adopted an appeasement strategy. He believes America's role as leader in the world is a thing of the past. I believe a strong America must - and will - lead the future.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>77</id>
		<author>Mitt Romney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The words spoken by the leader of the free world can expand the frontiers of freedom or shrink them. When Ronald Reagan called on Gorbachev to 'tear down this wall', a surge of confidence rose that would ultimately breach the bounds of the evil empire.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>78</id>
		<author>Mother Jones</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I believe that no man who holds a leader's position should ever accept favors from either side. He is then committed to show favors. A leader must stand alone.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>79</id>
		<author>Richard M. Nixon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I'm glad I'm not Brezhnev. Being the Russian leader in the Kremlin. You never know if someone's tape recording what you say.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>80</id>
		<author>Lewis H. Lapham</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership consists not in degrees of technique but in traits of character; it requires moral rather than athletic or intellectual effort, and it imposes on both leader and follower alike the burdens of self-restraint.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>81</id>
		<author>Hillary Clinton</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>My feeling is if you're going to be a leader, you have to carefully assess where people are and where people want to go.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>82</id>
		<author>Paul McCartney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I definitely did look up to John. We all looked up to John. He was older and he was very much the leader; he was the quickest wit and the smartest.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>83</id>
		<author>Daisaku Ikeda</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A person, who no matter how desperate the situation, gives others hope, is a true leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>84</id>
		<author>Wiz Khalifa</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>'Khalifa' is Arabic, it means successor, leader, shining light. My granddad is Muslim and he gave me that name.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>85</id>
		<author>Michael J. Fox</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I don't look at myself as a leader. I do look at myself as part of a community.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>86</id>
		<author>Norman Schwarzkopf</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>To be an effective leader, you have to have a manipulative streak - you have to figure out the people working for you and give each tasks that will take advantage of his strength.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>87</id>
		<author>Walter Lippmann</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The genius of a good leader is to leave behind him a situation which common sense, without the grace of genius, can deal with successfully.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>88</id>
		<author>Hillary Clinton</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>We would very much like to see Iran take a position as a responsible leader that doesn't intimidate or threaten or scare its neighbors and others. But the choice is really up to Iran and we're going to keep working to try to come out with the right decision.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>89</id>
		<author>Toni Morrison</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Somebody has to take responsibility for being a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>90</id>
		<author>Neale Donald Walsch</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I was told to challenge every spiritual teacher, every world leader to utter the one sentence that no religion, no political party, and no nation on the face of the earth will dare utter: 'Ours is not a better way, ours is merely another way.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>91</id>
		<author>Ziggy Marley</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am a leader. Leaders always get heat. They're always going against the grain. Jimi Hendrix got heat; Bob Marley got heat; Miles Davis got heat. Every great artist got heat. Heat means you're doing something right.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>92</id>
		<author>Ralph Nader</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader has the vision and conviction that a dream can be achieved. He inspires the power and energy to get it done.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>93</id>
		<author>John Henrik Clarke</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>In order to have a charismatic leader, you have to have a charismatic program. Because if you have a charismatic program, then if you can read you can lead. When the leader gets killed while you're reading from page 13 of your charismatic program, you can bury the man with honors, then continue the plan by reading from page 14. Let's keep on.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>94</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The quality of a leader cannot be judged by the answers he gives, but by the questions he asks.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>95</id>
		<author>Henry Louis Gates</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>People are afraid, and when people are afraid, when their pie is shrinking, they look for somebody to hate. They look for somebody to blame. And a real leader speaks to anxiety and to fear and allays those fears, assuages anxiety.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>96</id>
		<author>Conan O'Brien</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Fish recognize a bad leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>97</id>
		<author>Norman Schwarzkopf</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I've got to tell you what, the soldier doesn't fight very hard for a leader who is going to shoot him, okay, on his own whim. That's not what military leadership is all about.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>98</id>
		<author>Blaine Lee</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The leader who exercises power with honor will work from the inside out, starting with himself.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>99</id>
		<author>Vladimir Putin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If you aspire to be a leader of your own country, you must speak your own language, for God's sake.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>100</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Though there are lessons that can be learned about becoming a great leader, most exist inherently in the bellies of those who lead.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>101</id>
		<author>Jack Welch</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>In my lifetime, Mitt Romney is the most qualified leader I've ever seen run for the presidency of the United States.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>102</id>
		<author>Louis Farrakhan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Qaddafi is hated because he is the leader of a small country that is rich, but he uses his money to finance liberation struggles.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>103</id>
		<author>Joseph B. Wirthlin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The Savior encouraged brotherhood. He was not a long-distance leader. He walked and worked with those whom he led. He was not afraid of close friendships. He spent many hours with his disciples, and his relationships with them were intimate.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>104</id>
		<author>Brene Brown</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>To me, a leader is someone who holds her- or himself accountable for finding potential in people and processes. And so what I think is really important is sustainability.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>105</id>
		<author>Manny Pacquiao</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The most important thing as a leader is your relationship with God.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>106</id>
		<author>Marguerite Young</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If you understand hallucination and illusion, you don't blindly follow any leader. You must know if the person is sane or insane, over the abyss.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>107</id>
		<author>Andre Malraux</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The first duty of a leader is to make himself be loved without courting love. To be loved without 'playing up' to anyone - even to himself.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>108</id>
		<author>Gordon B. Hinckley</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It has been my privilege on various occasions to converse with presidents of the United States and important men in other governments. At the close of each such occasion, I have reflected on the rewarding experience of standing with confidence in the presence of an acknowledged leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>109</id>
		<author>Louis Farrakhan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>They should regard me as what I am. I am a spiritual leader and teacher.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>110</id>
		<author>Vladimir Putin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It's a historical phenomenon that in 250 years, a nation could move from a colony into the most prosperous nation of the world and the leader of the world. It is indeed an achievement, a tribute to the talent of the American nation, the American people and an optimal political and economic system.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>111</id>
		<author>Aneurin Bevan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I know that the right kind of political leader for the Labour Party is a desiccated calculating machine.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>112</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Notoriously outspoken, his sentences always punctuated with profanities, General George S. Patton was the epitome of what a leader should be like - or so he thought. Patton believed a leader should look and act tough, so he cultivated his image and his personality to match his philosophy.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>113</id>
		<author>Oriana Fallaci</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Whether it comes from a despotic sovereign or an elected president, from a murderous general or a beloved leader, I see power as an inhuman and hateful phenomenon.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>114</id>
		<author>Joshua Chamberlain</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I never could be a partisan leader - a man of one idea.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>115</id>
		<author>Courtney Love</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Being a rock star is like being a cult leader - you really have to be in your own religion.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>116</id>
		<author>Malala Yousafzai</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I have learned so much from Nelson Mandela, and he has been my leader. He is a perpetual inspiration for me and millions of others around the world.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>117</id>
		<author>Ziggy Marley</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am a leader, so leaders always get heat. They're always going against the grain. Jimi Hendrix got heat; Bob Marley got heat; Miles Davis got heat. Every great artist got heat. Heat means you're doing something right.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>118</id>
		<author>Yao Ming</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A good leader must be fair.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>119</id>
		<author>Martha Beck</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>All religious leaders and spiritual teachers emphasize finding a place within us that is true. People who obsessively follow these leaders instead of their own purpose attach to the spiritual leader and become fanatical and controlling. That's why Jesus tried to tell his followers not to get attached to outward form.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>120</id>
		<author>Tony Blair</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think the journey for a politician goes from wanting to please all the people all the time, to a political leader that realises in the end his responsibility is to decide. And when he decides, he divides.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>121</id>
		<author>George Clooney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The problem is, we elected a manager and we need a leader. Let's face it: Bush is just dim.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>122</id>
		<author>Tony Abbott</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The Australian public are very fair and they are always prepared to give the leader of a major political party a fair go.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>123</id>
		<author>George Edward Woodberry</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>From the beginning, about the rude altar of the god, to the days of Goethe, of Leopardi, and of Victor Hugo, the poet is the leader in the dance of life; and the phrase by which we name his singularity, the poetic temperament, denotes the primacy of that passion in his blood with which the frame of other men is less richly charged.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>124</id>
		<author>Ian Mckellen</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It was wrongly assumed that I wished to become some sort of leader among gay activists, whereas in reality I was happier to be a foot soldier.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>125</id>
		<author>Warren Bennis</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Becoming a leader is synonymous with becoming yourself. It is precisely that simple, and it is also that difficult.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>126</id>
		<author>Robin S. Sharma</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>There is a new model of leadership in the world that rides on the premise that every single person in the organisation can be a leader. Titles are important for structure and order, but real power does not come from titles.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>127</id>
		<author>Buzz Aldrin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>There's no doubt who was a leader in space after the Apollo Program. Nobody came close to us. And our education system, in science, technology, engineering and math, was at the top of the world. It's no longer there. We're descending rather rapidly.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>128</id>
		<author>Tom Peters</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As far as I'm concerned, the first business leader who was able to establish a cult of personality around his tenure was Lee Iacocca.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>129</id>
		<author>Warren Bennis</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The manager asks how and when; the leader asks what and why.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>130</id>
		<author>Nile Rodgers</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>My childhood was bittersweet in many ways. We moved around a lot. By the time I was 10, I had travelled thousands of miles, often on my own. My parents were like my friends, so it felt like I didn't really have parents at all. But in a crazy way that was very liberating. It forced me to be independent, maybe a leader, and certainly a survivor.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>131</id>
		<author>Cesar Millan</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Owners lavish love on their pets, which is why so many go from non-aggressive pups to being out of control when they're older. People just don't realise their dog must respect them as leader of the pack.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>132</id>
		<author>Oriana Fallaci</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Khomeini was not a puppet like Arafat or Qaddafi or the many other dictators I met in the Islamic world. He was a sort of Pope, a sort of king - a real leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>133</id>
		<author>Joel A. Barker</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is a person you will follow to a place you wouldn't go by yourself.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>134</id>
		<author>Mark McKinnon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Now personally, I think the president should golf every day and never have a press conference. I want the leader of the free world to be as stress-free as possible. And if golf helps fade the psychic heat from the job, by all means tee it up often, Mr. President.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>135</id>
		<author>Nick Clegg</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>When I became leader, I made very clear I was not going to choose the easy life. I have always taken risks. I don't like comfort-zone politics.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>136</id>
		<author>Timothy Noah</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Whenever a Kurd wants to measure the depth of some foreign leader's commitment to Kurdish autonomy, he listens for one particular word. That word is 'federal.' Anyone who will say he favors Kurdish federalism can be counted a friend of the Kurds.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>137</id>
		<author>Kevin O'Leary</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A lot of people have said a lot of great things about Steve Jobs. And for good reason: he built the world's second-most valuable company, with billions in profits and products that have improved every aspect of our lives. But Steve didn't get there by being a soft, fluffy, Kumbaya-type leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>138</id>
		<author>Robert Reich</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is someone who steps back from the entire system and tries to build a more collaborative, more innovative system that will work over the long term.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>139</id>
		<author>Ron Fournier</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The 2016 presidential election is ripe for the emergence of a game-changing political leader who either dramatically reforms one of the existing parties or mounts an independent bid.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>140</id>
		<author>Jane D. Hull</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Arizona is a national leader in school choice with both charter schools and tuition tax credits giving parents and their children more school choices than ever before.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>141</id>
		<author>Ted Cruz</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The grass roots are energized because the absolutely highest priority in the country in November is to defeat Barack Obama. I have spoken with literally thousands and thousands of tea-party activists - I have yet to meet a single tea-party leader that is not going to vote for Mitt Romney.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>142</id>
		<author>Steve Ballmer</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Our mail product, Hotmail, is the market leader globally.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>143</id>
		<author>Marina Abramovic</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am not a therapist. I am not a spiritual leader. These elements are in the art: it is therapeutic, spiritual, social and political - everything. It has many layers. But art has to have many layers. If it doesn't, then forget it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>144</id>
		<author>Sugar Ray Leonard</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Without boxing, because of my neighborhoods, who knows what would have happened to me. It was always about following the leader. And I definitely was not a leader. Boxing gave me discipline; a sense of self. It made me more outspoken. It gave me more confidence.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>145</id>
		<author>Bill O'Reilly</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Looking back, I clearly understand that seeing a 'chain of command' approach in my house was a positive thing for me. My father provided a strong point of view on life and was a leader. Boys, especially, need that.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>146</id>
		<author>Richard Foster</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think of Pope Gregory the Great. He wanted the cloister. He wanted to pray and study, and yet he was thrust into this administrative job, and he submitted to that. And in that submission, he became a great leader. You could say that the only person who is safe to lead is the person who is free to submit.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>147</id>
		<author>Anne Sweeney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think the must-have power qualities for a female or male power leader are really the ability to focus, to work hard, to be extremely goal oriented and to not let the noise and the nonsense interfere with your mission - what you really feel you want to do with your career and your life.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>148</id>
		<author>Pele</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The level of football in England is the top. English football is the leader in the world.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>149</id>
		<author>Henry Louis Gates</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Fortunately, in President Obama, the child of an African and an American, we finally have a leader who is uniquely positioned to bridge the great reparations divide.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>150</id>
		<author>Ray Kroc</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>151</id>
		<author>John Quincy Adams</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>152</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way, and shows the way.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>153</id>
		<author>Arnold H. Glasow</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A good leader takes a little more than his share of the blame, a little less than his share of the credit.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>154</id>
		<author>Steve Jobs</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>155</id>
		<author>Lao Tzu</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>156</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Teamwork makes the dream work, but a vision becomes a nightmare when the leader has a big dream and a bad team.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>157</id>
		<author>Martin Luther King, Jr.</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A genuine leader is not a searcher for consensus but a molder of consensus.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>158</id>
		<author>Max de Pree</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The first responsibility of a leader is to define reality. The last is to say thank you. In between, the leader is a servant.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>159</id>
		<author>Henry A. Kissinger</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The task of the leader is to get his people from where they are to where they have not been.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>160</id>
		<author>Theodore Roosevelt</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>People ask the difference between a leader and a boss. The leader leads, and the boss drives.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>161</id>
		<author>A. P. J. Abdul Kalam</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Let me define a leader. He must have vision and passion and not be afraid of any problem. Instead, he should know how to defeat it. Most importantly, he must work with integrity.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>162</id>
		<author>Muhammad Iqbal</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I lead no party; I follow no leader. I have given the best part of my life to careful study of Islam, its law and polity, its culture, its history and its literature.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>163</id>
		<author>Tupac Shakur</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think I'm a natural-born leader. I know how to bow down to authority if it's authority that I respect.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>164</id>
		<author>Colin Powell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think whether you're having setbacks or not, the role of a leader is to always display a winning attitude.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>165</id>
		<author>Ken Robinson</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The role of a creative leader is not to have all the ideas; it's to create a culture where everyone can have ideas and feel that they're valued.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>166</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Good leaders must communicate vision clearly, creatively, and continually. However, the vision doesn't come alive until the leader models it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>167</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader's job is not to do the work for others, it's to help others figure out how to do it themselves, to get things done, and to succeed beyond what they thought possible.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>168</id>
		<author>Andrew Carnegie</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>No man will make a great leader who wants to do it all himself or get all the credit for doing it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>169</id>
		<author>Buddha</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am not the first Buddha who came upon Earth, nor shall I be the last. In due time, another Buddha will arise in the world - a Holy One, a supremely enlightened One, endowed with 	wisdom in conduct, auspicious, knowing the universe, an incomparable leader of men, a master of angels and mortals.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>170</id>
		<author>Saint Teresa of Avila</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If Christ Jesus dwells in a man as his friend and noble leader, that man can endure all things, for Christ helps and strengthens us and never abandons us. He is a true friend.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>171</id>
		<author>Fetty Wap</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Fetty Wap is a soldier, father, a mentor, a leader for people that I never thought I'd be a leader for. A role model. A son. When you think of Fetty Wap, think of the soldier that ain't 	never quit and never listened to what they said about me or what the critics said about me or what I looked like or how people take me. I still will never quit.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>172</id>
		<author>Henry A. Kissinger</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader does not deserve the name unless he is willing occasionally to stand alone.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>173</id>
		<author>Theodore Roosevelt</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Appraisals are where you get together with your team leader and agree what an outstanding member of the team you are, how much your contribution has been valued, what massive potential 	you have and, in recognition of all this, would you mind having your salary halved.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>174</id>
		<author>Warren Bennis</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The manager accepts the status quo; the leader challenges it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>175</id>
		<author>John Lennon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>My role in society, or any artist's or poet's role, is to try and express what we all feel. Not to tell people how to feel. Not as a preacher, not as a leader, but as a reflection of us 	all.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>176</id>
		<author>Ferdinand Marcos</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership is the other side of the coin of loneliness, and he who is a leader must always act alone. And acting alone, accept everything alone.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>177</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>People buy into the leader before they buy into the vision.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>178</id>
		<author>Napoleon Bonaparte</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is a dealer in hope.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>179</id>
		<author>Muammar al-Gaddafi</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am an international leader, the dean of the Arab rulers, the king of kings of Africa and the imam of Muslims, and my international status does not allow me to descend to a lower level.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>180</id>
		<author>Gretchen Rubin</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>No leader did more for his country than Winston Churchill. Brave, magnanimous, traditional, he was like a king-general from Britain's heroic past. His gigantic qualities set him apart 	from ordinary humanity; there seemed no danger he feared, no effort too great for his limitless energies.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>181</id>
		<author>Benazir Bhutto</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As a woman leader, I thought I brought a different kind of leadership. I was interested in women's issues, in bringing down the population growth rate... as a woman, I entered politics 	with an additional dimension - that of a mother.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>182</id>
		<author>Colin Powell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If a leader doesn't convey passion and intensity then there will be no passion and intensity within the organization and they'll start to fall down and get depressed.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>183</id>
		<author>Mary Kay Ash</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The speed of the leader is the speed of the gang.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>184</id>
		<author>Mike Huckabee</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is the one who can outline the broad vision and the direction, and say here's where we are going to go, here's why we need to go there, and here's how we are going to get 	there. A manager is the one who actually gets up under the hood and tunes the carburetor.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>185</id>
		<author>Benjamin Carson</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think one of the keys to leadership is recognizing that everybody has gifts and talents. A good leader will learn how to harness those gifts toward the same goal.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>186</id>
		<author>Andrea Jung</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>There are pros and cons of experience. A con is that you can't look at the business with a fresh pair of eyes and as objectively as if you were a new CEO. Fire yourself on a Friday 	night and come in on Monday morning as if a search firm put you there as a turn-around leader. Can you be objective and make the bold change?</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>187</id>
		<author>Graydon Carter</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Arrogance, ignorance, and incompetence. Not a pretty cocktail of personality traits in the best of situations. No sirree. Not a pretty cocktail in an office-mate and not a pretty 	cocktail in a head of state. In fact, in a leader, it's a lethal cocktail.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>188</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The best way a mentor can prepare another leader is to expose him or her to other great people.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>189</id>
		<author>Richard M. Nixon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If an individual wants to be a leader and isn't controversial, that means he never stood for anything.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>190</id>
		<author>Colin Powell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>In other words, don't expect to always be great. Disappointments, failures and setbacks are a normal part of the lifecycle of a unit or a company and what the leader has to do is 	constantly be up and say 'we have a problem, let's go and get it'.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>191</id>
		<author>Brian Tracy</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The true measure of the value of any business leader and manager is performance.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>192</id>
		<author>Margaret Fuller</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Today a reader, tomorrow a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>193</id>
		<author>Indra Nooyi</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership is hard to define and good leadership even harder. But if you can get people to follow you to the ends of the earth, you are a great leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>194</id>
		<author>Howard Schultz</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The hardest thing about being a leader is demonstrating or showing vulnerability... When the leader demonstrates vulnerability and sensibility and brings people together, the team wins.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>195</id>
		<author>Rudy Giuliani</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>here are many qualities that make a great leader. But having strong beliefs, being able to stick with them through popular and unpopular times, is the most important characteristic of a great leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>196</id>
		<author>Colin Powell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Never neglect details. When everyone's mind is dulled or distracted the leader must be doubly vigilant.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>197</id>
		<author>Golda Meir</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader who doesn't hesitate before he sends his nation into battle is not fit to be a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>198</id>
		<author>Gary Hamel</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>oday, no leader can afford to be indifferent to the challenge of engaging employees in the work of creating the future. Engagement may have been optional in the past, but it's pretty much the whole game today.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>199</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As a leader, the first person I need to lead is me. The first person that I should try to change is me.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>200</id>
		<author>Henry Miller</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The real leader has no need to lead - he is content to point the way.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>201</id>
		<author>Sam Houston</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is someone who helps improve the lives of other people or improve the system they live under.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>202</id>
		<author>Vicente del Bosque</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader is admired, a boss is feared.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>203</id>
		<author>Bob Marley</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>eople want to listen to a message, word from Jah. This could be passed through me or anybody. I am not a leader. Messenger. The words of the songs, not the person, is what attracts people.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>204</id>
		<author>Lao Tzu</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>When the best leader's work is done the people say, 'We did it ourselves.'</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>205</id>
		<author>Jack Welch</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>was never the smartest guy in the room. From the first person I hired, I was never the smartest guy in the room. And that's a big deal. And if you're going to be a leader - if you're a leader and you're the smartest guy in the world - in the room, you've got real problems.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>206</id>
		<author>Zig Ziglar</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It is true that integrity alone won't make you a leader, but without integrity you will never be one.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>207</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>ne of the best paradoxes of leadership is a leader's need to be both stubborn and open-minded. A leader must insist on sticking to the vision and stay on course to the destination. But he must be open-minded during the process.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>208</id>
		<author>Robert Baden-Powell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Show me a poorly uniformed troop and I'll show you a poorly uniformed leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>209</id>
		<author>John F. Tierney</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>on education, in order to ensure that America remains a world leader, we must create an educated, skilled workforce in the vital areas of science, math, engineering and information technology. At the same time, we must give every student access to a college degree.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>210</id>
		<author>Mikhail Gorbachev</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>on the day I became Soviet leader, in March 1985, I had a special meeting with the leaders of the Warsaw Pact countries and told them: 'You are independent, and we are independent. You are responsible for your policies, we are responsible for ours. We will not intervene in your affairs, I promise you.'</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>211</id>
		<author>Nigel Farage</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>we have a Conservative leader that believes in green taxes, that won't bring back grammar schools, that believes in continuing with total open-door migration from eastern Europe and refuses to give us a referendum on the EU.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>212</id>
		<author>Dalai Lama</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>World belongs to humanity, not this leader, that leader or that king or prince or religious leader. World belongs to humanity.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>213</id>
		<author>Dustin Diamond</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I'm a shepherd, not a sheep, and I've always prided myself on being a leader and not a follower.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>214</id>
		<author>Tacitus</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Reason and judgment are the qualities of a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>215</id>
		<author>Indra Nooyi</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>as a leader, I am tough on myself and I raise the standard for everybody; however, I am very caring because I want people to excel at what they are doing so that they can aspire to be me in the future.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>216</id>
		<author>Nelson Mandela</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I was not a messiah, but an ordinary man who had become a leader because of extraordinary circumstances.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>217</id>
		<author>Nelson Mandela</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>There are times when a leader must move out ahead of the flock, go off in a new direction, confident that he is leading his people the right way.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>218</id>
		<author>Jawaharlal Nehru</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>A leader or a man of action in a crisis almost always acts subconsciously and then thinks of the reasons for his action.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>219</id>
		<author>Anthony J. D'Angelo</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>You don't have to hold a position in order to be a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>220</id>
		<author>Richard Foster</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership is an act of submission to God. To be a leader means listening to all kinds of people and situations. Out of that listening, we are hoping to discern the mind of God as best we can. This is the price of leadership - it's an act of sacrifice. So leadership is part and parcel of the work of submission to God.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>221</id>
		<author>Sheri L. Dew</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>There is no greater name for a leader than mother or father. There is no leadership more important than parenthood.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>222</id>
		<author>Simon Sinek</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Like a good parent can't also be his child's best friend, a leader with authority requires some separation from subordinates.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>223</id>
		<author>Dee Dee Myers</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I am endlessly fascinated that playing football is considered a training ground for leadership, but raising children isn't. Hey, it made me a better leader: you have to take a lot of people's needs into account; you have to look down the road. Trying to negotiate getting a couple of kids to watch the same TV show requires serious diplomacy.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>224</id>
		<author>Plato</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>When the tyrant has disposed of foreign enemies by conquest or treaty, and there is nothing more to fear from them, then he is always stirring up some war or other, in order that the people may require a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>225</id>
		<author>Mike Krzyzewski</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Each group and each youngster is different. As a leader or coach, you get to know what they need.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>226</id>
		<author>Carl von Clausewitz</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Never forget that no military leader has ever become great without audacity.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>227</id>
		<author>Steve Nash</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Leadership is possible in all different ways, and in all different areas of life. Whether it is with friends or family, I expect them to set a great example for me, and hopefully I will do the same for them. And that is all part of being a leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>228</id>
		<author>Erik Erikson</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Every adult, whether he is a follower or a leader, a member of a mass or of an elite, was once a child. He was once small. A sense of smallness forms a substratum in his mind, ineradicably. His triumphs will be measured against this smallness; his defeats will substantiate it.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>229</id>
		<author>Robert Griffin III</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Sometimes people think it's what you say when you're in a huge group that makes you a leader. But sometimes it's the one-on-one conversations you have with guys individually, just getting to know them. I think I've done that a lot. Not intentionally - it just happens.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>230</id>
		<author>Mac Thornberry</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The day before the anniversary of D-Day, we lost a man who was equaled by few and surpassed by none as a leader in the cause of freedom: Ronald Reagan.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>231</id>
		<author>Gautam Gambhir</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>I think that a leader is someone that needs to make an impact on, off the cricket field and in their lives as well.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>232</id>
		<author>Douglas Conant</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>Ultimately as a leader, you're evaluated on how you interact with people. If you do it well, you develop a reputation as effective leader. If you don't, you develop a reputation for being a highly ineffective leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>233</id>
		<author>Ken Blanchard</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>In the past a leader was a boss. Today's leaders must be partners with their people... they no longer can lead solely based on positional power.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>234</id>
		<author>Woodrow Wilson</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The ear of the leader must ring with the voices of the people.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>235</id>
		<author>John C. Maxwell</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>All good leaders are connectors. They relate well and make people feel confident about themselves and their leader.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>236</id>
		<author>Xenophon</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The true test of a leader is whether his followers will adhere to his cause from their own volition, enduring the most arduous hardships without being forced to do so, and remaining steadfast in the moments of greatest peril.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>237</id>
		<author>Morgan Wootten</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>To be successful in coaching you have to treat your team like a family. The leader needs backing from everyone.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>238</id>
		<author>Anna Wintour</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>It's very important to take risks. I think that research is very important, but in the end you have to work from your instinct and feeling and take those risks and be fearless. When I hear a company is being run by a team, my heart sinks, because you need to have that leader with a vision and heart that can move things forward.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>239</id>
		<author>Carl von Clausewitz</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>If the leader is filled with high ambition and if he pursues his aims with audacity and strength of will, he will reach them in spite of all obstacles.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>240</id>
		<author>Joe Namath</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>To be a leader, you have to make people want to follow you, and nobody wants to follow someone who doesn't know where he is going.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>241</id>
		<author>Heather Bresch</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>As a leader, these attributes - confidence, perseverance, work ethic and good sense - are all things I look for in people. I also try to lead by example and create an environment where good questions and good ideas can come from anyone.</jokeText>
	</joke>
	<joke>
		<id>242</id>
		<author>Lao Tzu</author>
		<date>03.01.2015</date>
		<jokeText>The wicked leader is he who the people despise. The good leader is he who the people revere. The great leader is he who the people say, 'We did it ourselves.'</jokeText>
	</joke>
</jokes>